<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Poney Island</title>
    <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Poney Island</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Dont Care for Your Privacy</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</guid>
      <description>The Maslow pyramid
Social Media lures you to believe they care for your wellness Over the years, Social Media has hired Neuroscientists to make their platform so addictive that the psychological needs has been revisited and took priority over Security and safety. How secure and how private is our data matters less then our perception of privacy and security; and therefore while we focus less in Digital Safety then our needs for digital social interaction, social media invests more into Public Relationship, lawyers, marketing and lobbyist to secure their reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Privacy Laws a Joke About Privacy?</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 05:32:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</guid>
      <description>You dont read Terms and Conditions of services you use  Let&amp;rsquo;s face the reality, you can&amp;rsquo;t read 20 min of Terms and Conditions in 2 seconds every website or services you visit
 Have you actually, once in your life, seriously read one with all the attention it deserves to fully understand at which extent your privacy is at stake? I did it couple of times before I realized how vain effort it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 20:32:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/test3/</guid>
      <description>Curabitur laoreet nec libero at condimentum. Sed ultrices dui eget sapien facilisis sagittis. Donec rhoncus auctor ligula ut dapibus. Curabitur ut dapibus eros, non euismod arcu. Donec dictum auctor sem, ut accumsan magna fringilla ut. Phasellus sit amet tincidunt leo. Cras maximus, dolor nec tincidunt maximus, massa eros fringilla sapien, et commodo eros tellus at leo. Cras elementum tempor commodo. Sed in arcu eu metus placerat volutpat vitae eu arcu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/02/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 13:45:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/02/test/</guid>
      <description>Curabitur tincidunt, eros ut tincidunt efficitur, eros enim mollis ligula, vitae aliquet augue magna at magna. Phasellus augue metus, blandit ut dignissim quis, pulvinar eget nisl. Nulla sodales malesuada ornare. Aenean suscipit, erat at suscipit feugiat, massa lorem scelerisque enim, non sodales est lacus sit amet velit. Phasellus gravida nulla ut dictum mollis. Aliquam interdum porta turpis, sed bibendum nunc aliquam a. Cras et porta ante. Curabitur eget purus nulla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test 2</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/01/test-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 20:15:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/01/test-2/</guid>
      <description>Intro Curabitur tincidunt, eros ut tincidunt efficitur, eros enim mollis ligula, vitae aliquet augue magna at magna. Phasellus augue metus, blandit ut dignissim quis, pulvinar eget nisl. Nulla sodales malesuada ornare. Aenean suscipit, erat at suscipit feugiat, massa lorem scelerisque enim, non sodales est lacus sit amet velit. Phasellus gravida nulla ut dictum mollis. Aliquam interdum porta turpis, sed bibendum nunc aliquam a. Cras et porta ante. Curabitur eget purus nulla.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
