<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Poney Island</title>
    <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Poney Island</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Dont Care for Your Privacy</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</guid>
      <description>The Maslow pyramid
Social Media lures you to believe they care for your wellness Over the years, Social Media has hired Neuroscientists to make their platform so addictive that the psychological needs has been revisited and took priority over Security and safety. How secure and how private is our data matters less then our perception of privacy and security; and therefore while we focus less in Digital Safety then our needs for digital social interaction, social media invests more into Public Relationship, lawyers, marketing and lobbyist to secure their reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Privacy Laws a Joke About Privacy?</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 05:32:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</guid>
      <description>You dont read Terms and Conditions of services you use  Let&amp;rsquo;s face the reality, you can&amp;rsquo;t read 20 min of Terms and Conditions in 2 seconds every website or services you visit
 Have you actually, once in your life, seriously read one with all the attention it deserves to fully understand at which extent your privacy is at stake? I did it couple of times before I realized how vain effort it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 20:32:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/09/test3/</guid>
      <description>Suspendisse dignissim dignissim enim non imperdiet. Cras tristique, enim non rutrum tempor, purus leo imperdiet lorem, imperdiet sollicitudin diam nunc a purus. Aliquam posuere risus vitae quam luctus aliquet. Nullam pretium nunc velit, at aliquam tellus finibus in. Pellentesque consectetur elit sed sapien iaculis fermentum. Vestibulum at dolor eu nunc gravida dignissim non eget nibh. Donec neque lorem, fringilla ut enim quis, faucibus tincidunt nunc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/02/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 13:45:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/02/test/</guid>
      <description>Nullam id lorem vel quam porttitor pretium eu ac velit. Etiam felis libero, tristique id laoreet ut, vehicula eu ligula. Proin facilisis dignissim sollicitudin. Maecenas eget urna scelerisque, laoreet velit at, placerat dolor. Fusce fermentum commodo mollis. Nam a ultricies sapien. Pellentesque tempus odio sit amet tortor tincidunt, at tristique purus tincidunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test 2</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/01/test-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 20:15:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/devdraft/posts/2021/01/test-2/</guid>
      <description>Intro Sed consectetur enim non erat mattis pretium. Morbi faucibus tellus ac ipsum molestie, ac sagittis ligula molestie. Mauris sed placerat elit. Ut eleifend dolor odio. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Sed dapibus porttitor tortor eu venenatis. Donec lacus mi, rhoncus nec iaculis condimentum, maximus nec ipsum. Aliquam eu nisl commodo, varius ligula eu, faucibus dui.
Title 1 Nam quis suscipit lacus. Nullam hendrerit massa ligula, vel finibus nisl rhoncus in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
