<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Poney Island</title>
    <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Poney Island</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Dont Care for Your Privacy</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:05:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/social-media-dont-care-for-your-privacy/</guid>
      <description>The Maslow pyramid
Social Media lures you to believe they care for your wellness Over the years, Social Media has hired Neuroscientists to make their platform so addictive that the psychological needs has been revisited and took priority over Security and safety. How secure and how private is our data matters less then our perception of privacy and security; and therefore while we focus less in Digital Safety then our needs for digital social interaction, social media invests more into Public Relationship, lawyers, marketing and lobbyist to secure their reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Privacy Laws a Joke About Privacy?</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 05:32:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/are-privacy-laws-a-joke-about-privacy/</guid>
      <description>You dont read Terms and Conditions of services you use  Let&amp;rsquo;s face the reality, you can&amp;rsquo;t read 20 min of Terms and Conditions in 2 seconds every website or services you visit
 Have you actually, once in your life, seriously read one with all the attention it deserves to fully understand at which extent your privacy is at stake? I did it couple of times before I realized how vain effort it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 20:32:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/09/test3/</guid>
      <description>Nullam id lorem vel quam porttitor pretium eu ac velit. Etiam felis libero, tristique id laoreet ut, vehicula eu ligula. Proin facilisis dignissim sollicitudin. Maecenas eget urna scelerisque, laoreet velit at, placerat dolor. Fusce fermentum commodo mollis. Nam a ultricies sapien. Pellentesque tempus odio sit amet tortor tincidunt, at tristique purus tincidunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/02/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 13:45:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/02/test/</guid>
      <description>Proin sit amet libero eleifend, eleifend eros ut, imperdiet mauris. Nam at massa nec lectus tempus ullamcorper ut id odio. Cras finibus lectus sit amet enim congue dictum. Phasellus malesuada sollicitudin metus non tincidunt. Vivamus purus quam, accumsan nec neque sed, aliquam suscipit nibh. Etiam blandit viverra lectus, ac rutrum mauris interdum sit amet. Curabitur mollis sem at accumsan dapibus. Nulla vel dolor elementum, pharetra metus cursus, gravida velit. Ut eget dolor vel risus molestie venenatis non sit amet ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test 2</title>
      <link>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/01/test-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 20:15:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xade1.github.io/$DEV_BASEURL/posts/2021/01/test-2/</guid>
      <description>Intro Aliquam sit amet felis euismod, varius odio ac, commodo ex. Maecenas quis felis ligula. Sed semper nisi et libero accumsan, id condimentum nisl tempus. Donec in elementum tortor, quis facilisis nunc. Duis sed malesuada metus. Vivamus sed dignissim felis, vitae fringilla metus. Pellentesque semper elit leo.
Title 1 Suspendisse in ligula convallis, maximus metus et, cursus velit. Aenean nec massa volutpat, lacinia lacus sit amet, tempus tellus. Etiam aliquet, est at volutpat faucibus, libero lectus ultrices leo, et tempus mi est eu quam.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
